# Shakhzodbek Yuldoshev

E-mail: yuldoshov.shakhzod@gmail.com Website: shakhzodbek.com

Phone: +99-899-517-58-63; +99-890-111- Address: Khorezm, Shovot, Fayzobod 7.

54-97

# Objective

I am a passionate Junior Full Stack Developer with strong knowledge and problem solving skills. I have practical experience with front end technologies like JavaScript, React.js, HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, figma, Git, netlify. I also have basic knowledge in backend and database technologies such as Java, Spring, Hibernate and PostgreSQL.

# Work experience

### **DATA** learning Centre

Aug 2020 — Present

Teaching Front end

Educating students in the Frontend area of web programming: I have taught these given technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Sass, JavaScript. Go, Figma, Netlify, Hosting.

### **OKS Technologies**

January 2020 — May 2020

Front-end developer

I basically convert web pages from simple graphical form to code and I have also divided web pages to separate components in React.

## Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- SASS
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Java
- Spring
- PostgreSQL
- Database
- Git
- Figma
- Netlify
- Hosting

Shakhzodhek Yuldoshev

# Education

## Full-stack web Development

Jan 2019 — Dec 2019

PDP IT Academy

I was awarded a Certificate for successful completion of full Stack Web Development course.

#### Natural sciences

Sen 2013 — May 2016

Academic Lyceum No. 2

I graduated with a degree in natural sciences and applied to study at the Institute of Medicine(T.T.A). But i didn't pass the exam several time and i decided to be a programmer and I got It.

# Languages

#### **English**

Intermediate

#### Uzbek

My native language. I can speak fluent in Uzbek language.

## Interests

Coding, Driving, painting, Reading, Cycling, Online gaming, Gadgets, Photography, Learning new things

Shakhzodbek Yuldoshev